<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">"Code De Pirates "</string>
    <string name="Instructions">
        1. Cheating is prohibited but of course if you are not caught it won\'t be counted\n
        2. After logging in time will start but waiting to start late will also be foolish attempt to save time\n
        3. Password to log in will be given to you so useless tries to log in won\'t help\n
        4. Try to avoid fast clicking here and there\n
        5. If disqualified you can restart but then you have to revisit all stations\n
        6. Avoid killing application or to change system settings in between\n
        7. Have fun. Its Compulsory.\n
        8. For help visit anytime to help center located at Amphitheater or call to given numbers\n
        9. Report any error if there in app to any volunteer\n
        10. Don\'t waste time reading these instructions, you will be given these instructions anyway at start of event\n\n
        That\'s it. Best of Luck.
    </string>
    <string name="Rules">
        \n
        1. Question will be displayed in Ques tab\n
        2. Dry run the code and find output\n
        3. Output will give the station number\n
        4. Find station number on Map and visit that center\n
        5. Volunteer there will enter a code in app and check that code\n
        6. You will be given code snippet to solve at spot\n
        7. You will be given master code snippet on success\n
        8. If code works next question will be generated and repeat process all over again to get all 16 snippets\n
        9. In end rearrange all snippets to generate master code\n
        10. Dry run master code and generate answer\n
        11. Enter answer in box and submit\n
        12. On success you will be given location to go or person to call and you are done\n\n
        Good Luck
    </string>
    <string name="about">
        Created by:\n\nRicha Jajoo\nChintan Shah\n\n
        Contact for feedback/query
    </string>
    <string name="Oops">Ooops! Time ended\nAnd it seems that you don\'t have all master code snippets\nHence you are disqualified</string>
    <string name="end">You got lost while finding Treasure and your ship sunk deep into ocean\n\nEnjoy this day at NU TECH cause\n\n\"Dying is the day worth living for\"</string>

</resources>
